这是什么？
So, now, what is this, now?
- 扭扭虫   - 哈哈
- Googlie Worm.     - Ha-ha-ha.
这个呢？
And this?
毛球
Glow Pop Jiggly Jam.
好好玩喔
Bait is so funny.
这是什么？
Hey, um, what's this?
去年剩的一块三明治
Oh, a hunk of sandwich from last year.
盖勒钓到了 看来是条大鱼
Oh, Geller's got one hooked. Oh! Looks like a big one. Oh! Oh!
经典的人鱼大战…
It's the classic struggle between man...
有人撞倒一盏台灯
Someone knocked over a lamp.
这次去钓鱼最棒的是…
Hey, you know what's gonna be great about the fishing trip?
到了湖中央 爸会问我"你都在忙什么"
When my dad gives me that, "Joey, what are you doing with your life?" stuff...
我可以说 我要跟却尔登希斯顿演电影
...I can say, "Well, I'm doing a movie with Charlton Heston, Dad.
- 你呢？ - 太棒了
- What are you doing with your life?"     - Aw.
别因为我出来就低气压
You don't have to stop having fun just because I'm here.
凯西没有背叛你们
Kathy didn't cheat on all of you.
除了你
Well, except you.
乔伊 你不该丢下钱德
I don't think you should leave Chandler alone.
他跟凯西才分手两天
It's only been two days since he broke up with Kathy.
下周再去钓鱼吧
You can go fishing next week.
我帮不上忙 他还穿着运动裤
There's nothing I can do right now. He's still in his sweatpants.
现在才第一阶段
That's only phase one.
我第二阶段会回来 我从不错过第二阶段
You know? I'll be back for phase two. I would never miss phase two.
什么第二阶段？
What's phase two?
喝个烂醉 上脱衣舞厅
Getting drunk and going to a strip club.
那怎么会有帮助？
How does going to a strip club make him better?
那里有裸女
There are naked ladies there.
然后就是第三阶段 对别的女人产生性幻想
It helps him get to phase three, picturing yourself with other women.
- 那个阶段也有裸女   - 对
- There are naked ladies there too.     - Yeah.
让我清静一下 好吗？
Would you give me one minute, please?
这跟你上星期挑的外套配？
So these will match the jacket you picked out for me last week?
这就对了…
There we go.
就是这样…
There it is.
- 你知道我需要什么吗？ - 什么？
- Oh, you know what I need?     - Yeah?
- 手套 棕色的皮手套   - 好
- Gloves. Brown leather dress gloves.     - Oh, okay.
我看看 这只手是大号
Uh, well, let's see. You're about a... Well, this one is large. Ha, ha.
这只手…
And, uh, this one...
- 也是大号？ - 对
- Also a large?     - Yeah. Okay.
- 好   - 两只大号的手套马上来
- Yeah.     - Two larges coming right up. Ha, ha.
- 瑞秋 耽误你下   - 好
- Rachel, could I have a moment?     - Yes.
我的侄女从伦敦来玩
I was wondering, my niece, you see, is in town from London.
她跟你差不多大
She's about your age, I'd say.
总之 我有两张歌剧的票
Anyway, I have tickets for the opera. Die Fledermaus.
《蝙蝠》 你今晚愿意陪她吗？
I was wondering if you would keep her company this evening.
- 好 没问题   - 太好了
- Sure. You got it.     - Oh, good.
太好了 算我一份 我和《蝙蝠》 太棒了
Count me in. Me, Fledermaus. Great. I really...
好 谢谢 谢谢 谢谢你
Oh, yes, of course. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so very much.
怎么样？
So?
怎样？
So...
- 手套？ - 对喔 我马上去拿
- Gloves?     - Oh, right. Sorry, I'll be right back.
其实我该走了
Actually, you know what? I gotta take off.
不晓得你今晚有没有事？
But I was curious, do you have any plans for tonight?
没有 没事
No, nothing.
我投资的夜总会今晚开慕 你要去吗？
I invested in this nightclub. Would you like to come?
好啊 太棒了
Yeah, that would be great.
你喜欢性虐待的主题吧？
You're into hard-core S and M, right?
- 应该…   - 开玩笑的
- Well, I guess.     - I'm kidding.
我会先到 我会把你列为贵宾 进来找我
I'm gonna put you on the VIP list, okay? Look for me.
- 好 没问题   - 晚上见
- Yeah. Great. You betcha.     - I'll see you tonight.
- 好   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
- 差点忘了给你票   - 什么？
- I almost forgot the tickets, didn't I?     - What?
你和艾蜜莉 今晚去看《蝙蝠》
For you and Emily. Tonight. Die Fledermaus.
对喔
Oh. Oh, right.
你一定会喜欢 三大男高音去了两个
I think you'll like it. It has two of the Three Tenors.
好耶
Okay.
凯西居然这样对我 我真的以为我要定下来了
I can't believe Kathy did this to me. I really thought that she was the one.
告诉你们
Well, I'll tell you what.
我再也不离开这张椅子了
From now on, I am not getting out of this chair, ever.
以后我要定在这张椅子上
Okay? From now on, this chair is the one.
还有这条运动裤
You know what else is the one? My sweatpants.
别这样 把运动裤脱掉
Come on, man, just take the sweats off, okay?
脱掉 我们来玩
Just take them off and we'll have some fun.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
- 有钓到大鱼吗？ - 说出来吓死你们
- Did you catch any big fish?     - Oh, my God, you guys have no idea.
- 哇   - 你好臭
- Oh, wow.     - Oh, my God, you stink.
搞什么？
Oh, are you kidding?
我三天没洗澡
Three days on the lake without a shower.
还掉进一桶鱼饵里
Plus, I fell into that big tub of worms at the bait stand.
他怎么样？
Hey, how's he doing?
坐在那里坐了两天
He hasn't gotten out of that chair in two days.
兄弟 你还好吗？
Ahem. Hey, buddy, how's it going?
好兄弟回家就没事了
You see that? He just needed his pal to come home.
我得背台词
I gotta go memorize my lines.
明天一早 要和却尔登希斯顿演戏
Me and Charlton Heston, bright and early tomorrow, baby.
- 好耶   - 好耶
- Yeah.     - Yeah.
嘿 嘿
- Hey. ROSS: Hey.
- 嘿   - 摩妮卡
- Hey.     - Hey, Monica.
- 怎么了？ - 噢…
- Uh-oh. What's the matter?     - Oh...
约书亚约我参加夜总会开慕
Joshua invited me to this fancy club opening tonight.
但我已经答应沃森先生
But I already told Mr. Waltham...
要带他的侄女去看老掉牙歌剧
...that I would take his niece to the dumb old opera.
能怎么办呢？
So, what are you gonna do?
- 我不知道   - 不行 救救我
- I don't know, sweetie.     - No. Help me.
- 我不行 我要工作   - 菲比？
- I can't. I have to work.     - Phoebe?
我很想 但我都在晚上害喜
I would, but I get my morning sickness in the evening.
除非她想整晚帮我捞住头发
Ooh, no, unless she wants to spend the night holding my hair back for me.
拜托啦 我一定要去找约书亚
Ugh. Gosh, you guys, come on. This is... I have to meet Joshua.
这样他才能看到有趣的瑞秋
This is my one chance for him to see the fun Rachel.
"娶来当老婆会很棒"的瑞秋
You know, the "Wouldn't it be great if she were my wife?" Rachel.
乔伊和钱德回来了吗？
Are Joey and Chandler back?
钱德还在第一阶段 乔伊正是臭味的来源
Oh, Chandler's still in phase one, and Joey's that thing you smell.
噢
Oh.
嗨
Hi.
所以… ？
So?
不要
No.
拜托啦
Oh, come on.
- 应该是她   - 等下 罗斯 拜托啦
- I think she's here.     - No, wait, wait, wait. Ross, please?
你要我带一个不认识的女生 去看歌剧
You want me to take some girl I've never met to the opera...
好让你去夜总会 跟某个男人打情骂俏？
...so you can go to a club and flirt with some guy?
真难决定啊
Hmm. Yeah, that is a toughie.
她在看走廊
Oh, she's looking down the hall.
她在看我
She looked right at me.
这样看是看不到的 对吧？
Oh, wait, you can't see people through that little hole, can you?
你好啊
Hello.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hello?     - Aah!
马上来 罗斯 拜托啦
Oh, I'll be right there. Okay, Ross, please. Come on.
我以为我们已经放得开了
I thought we had moved on.
我以为我们可以彼此祝福了
I thought we'd gotten to a place where we could be happy for each other.
难道只有我是？
I mean, was that just me?
- 好吧   - 谢谢你 谢谢
- All right, I'll do it.     - Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
- 艾蜜莉？ - 是
- Emily?     - Yes.
- 我是瑞秋葛林   - 谢天谢地
- I'm Rachel Green.     - Thank goodness.
计划有小小的变动 我晚上没空 所以…
There has been a teeny change of plans. It turns out I'm not free tonight, so...
是吗？
Really? Heh.
太好了 我一定是没接到电话 虽然我整天都没出门
That's lovely. I must have missed your call, even though I didn't leave the flat all day.
- 我… 不   - 这也没什么
- Well, no, I...     - No, no, no, that's not rude.
我来到这里
It's in keeping with a trip...
先是被你们的热狗车撞倒
...where I've already been run down by one of your wiener carts...
在机场又被脱衣服搜身
...and been strip-searched at John F. Kennedy Airport.
显然我长得就像
Apparently, I look like someone...
屁股里塞了古柯碱
...who's got a balloon full of cocaine stuffed up their bum.
我觉得你很漂亮啊
I think you look great.
再见 很高兴认识你们
Good night. It was very nice to meet you all.
我去追她
I'll get her.
- 快去   - 好
- Please hurry.     - Okay.
他们讲话好好玩
Don't you just love the way they talk?
怎么了？ 宝宝在踢
- What?     - It kicked. I think the baby kicked.
- 天啊   - 哈哈
- Oh, my God.     - Ha, ha.
不对 是内裤的松紧带断了
Oh, no, wait. Oh. That was the elastic in my underwear busted.
完了 我睡过头了
Oh, my God. I overslept.
通告是半小时前 我得赶快
I was supposed to be on the set a half an hour ago. I gotta get out of here.
你不能这样去 你好臭
What? Joey, you can't go like that. You stink.
我睡着忘记洗澡 现在没时间了
I fell asleep before I could shower. Now I don't have time.
才十条街 用跑的还来得及
They're 10 blocks away. If I run, I can make it.
跑十条卫会更臭
Yeah, run 10 blocks. That'll help the smell.
慢一点 不 你走吧
Hey. Whoa! Slow down. No, keep moving. Whoa.
- 昨晚怎么样啊？ - 我没见到约书亚
- So how did it go with Joshua last night?     - Oh. Well, I didn't see Joshua.
但我揍了一个女生一拳
But I did punch a girl in the face.
- 什么？ - 为什么？
- What?     - Why?
昨晚真的很倒楣 雨下得很大
The whole night was horrible. It was pouring rain.
到了现场 名单上没有瑞秋葛林 但有一佃瑞秋葛皮
And there was no Rachel Green on the list, but there was a Rachel Greep.
你有见到她吗？
Oh. So did you get to meet her?
根本没这个人 但有个女生听到了
No, there is no Rachel Greep. But then this other girl overheard us.
大叫"我就是瑞秋葛皮" 结果她就进去了
And she was all, "I'm Rachel Greep, I'm Rachel Greep," and he let her in.
所以你揍她？ 不是 她已经进去了
- So you hit her in the face?     - No, she was already in.
不过复面有个肥婆想偷我的伞
But then this big bitch behind me tried to steal my umbrella...
我扁了她
...so I clocked her.
我真不敢相信
Ugh. I can't believe this.
真是的 我只想在工作之余 跟约书亚相处一下
All I wanted was just a few hours outside of work to see Joshua...
好让他有机会爱上我
...so that he could go ahead and start falling in love with me.
菲比
Aw. Pheebs.
那是你的名字
Honey, that's your name.
我以为那是我们之间的昵称
That's short for Phoebe? I thought that's what we called each other.
你穿上裤子了 没错
MONICA: Hey, you're wearing pants.     - That's right.
男生呢？我要买醉看脱衣舞了
Where are the guys? I'm ready to get drunk and see strippers.
才早上9点半 那里有早餐吃到饱
- It's 9:30 in the morning.     - They got a breakfast buffet.
- 喂… 罗斯   - 让我跟他说
- Hello? Oh, hey, Ross.     - Ooh. Let me talk to him.
天哪
Oh, my God.
- 我能不能… ？ - 等等 什么？
- Can't I just...?     - Shh. Wait, what?
- 我的电话她还嘘我   - 别吵啦
- It's my phone and she's shush...     - Shh. Please.
他说什么？
What's he saying?
他跟艾蜜莉在佛蒙特投宿
He's with Emily at a bed and breakfast in Vermont.
什么？天哪
What? Oh, my God.
艾蜜莉是谁？不会吧
Who the hell is Emily? No.
他们在佛蒙特？怎么会？
They're in Vermont? How did this happen?
他怎么会跟那个巫婆去佛蒙特？
How did he end up in Vermont with that awful witch?
也许她没有一直打他吧
Maybe she doesn't hit him all the time.
我们见到她时…
When we met her...
她湿透了 连脚都是湿的
...she was soaking, her feet were wet.
谁不会脾气差啊？
Who wouldn't be miserable?
是真的 我一帮她换上干的鞋子 她整个人都不同了
Once I got her into a dry pair of shoes, she was a totally different person.
罗斯 快来 外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
Ross, come quickly. There's a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard.
我要挂了 外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
I gotta go! There's a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard!
他挂了 外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
He had to go. There was a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard.
我不懂 她很机车耶
I don't get this. She was horrible.
我要去站在那边
Okay, I'm gonna go stand over there.
- 你干嘛这么在乎？ - 我才不在乎
- Why do you care so much, anyway?     - I don't care.
我只是很气我跟约书亚没进展
You know what? I'm just upset that I'm getting nowhere with Joshua.
但哪有人一认识 就跑去佛蒙特的
Know what? Still, you do not just meet someone and go flitting off to Vermont.
你和贝瑞一认识就跑去维尔
Well, when you first met Barry, you flitted off to Vail.
你能不能偶尔有一次 不要什么小事都记得？
Ugh. You know, could you just for once not remember every little thing?
他什么时候回来？
So, you know, when's he getting back?
- 过两天吧   - 知道吗?
- A couple of days.     - Know what?
我就知道会这样
I knew something like this was gonna happen.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
钱德 你不能让阶段倒流
Chandler. You can't just go back a phase.
可以 时间才不能倒流
Yes, you can. You're thinking about time. You can't go back in time.
我们跟你去进行第二阶段好了
Why don't you just...? Why don't you do your phase-two strip-club thing with us?
- 对呀 我们可以当男生   - 你们不行
- Yeah, come on, we can be guys.     - Heh. No, you can't.
让我们当嘛 也许我们想当
Come on, let us be guys. Maybe we wanna be guys.
你们才不想
You don't wanna be guys.
全身是毛还短命
You'd be all hairy and you wouldn't live as long.
你…
You know, you...
别这么孬种
Would you just stop being such a wuss and get those off?
把运动裤脱掉 跟我们去看裸女跳舞
And you come with us and watch naked girls dance around.
好
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我是乔伊崔比亚尼 我来了
Hey, Joey Tribbiani. I'm here, I'm here.
别急 来得及 进度有点落复
Calm down, we got time. We're running a little late.
准备好了
All set.
你看 却尔登希斯顿在嚼甘草
Look at that. Charlton Heston eating a licorice whip.
他很爱嚼甘草 老是…
Yeah, he loves them. I've never seen him with...
搞什么？ 什么东西这么臭？
Whoa. Yeah. What the hell is that? What smells so bad?
- 是你   - 噢
- You.     - Oh.
难怪你会这么想 不过你知道其实是谁吗？
I could see why you would think that. But actually, you know who I think it is?
- 你？ - 不 是希斯顿
- You?     - No, no. It's Heston.
- 什么？ - 他臭死了
- What?     - The man reeks.
他臭得好像去钓了三天′鱼 现在还嚼甘草
Smells like he went on a three-day fishing trip and then ate licorice. Ick.
不可能
There's no way he smells.
只有他的休息室有浴室
He's the only one around here with a shower in his dressing room.
真的？浴室？是哪间？
Really? A shower, huh? And, uh, which room might that be?
门口有写"希斯顿"的那间
The one with "Heston" on it.
有意思
Interesting.
去吧 好好放松
Gonna take my time
我换了零钞 你要不要去塞她的小裤裤？
Hey. I got some ones. You wanna put them in her panties?
不用了 娘
No, thanks, Mom.
抱歉
Oh. No. Um, hi. That, that.
你得熄掉 我怀孕了
You have to put that out because I'm pregnant, so...
也许你和你的孩子应该去别家
Well, maybe you and your baby ought to go to another strip club.
这才不是我的孩子
Heh, heh. It's not my baby. Heh, heh.
很好
Very good. Yes. That was so good.
太棒了 我喜欢 很火辣
Really, really enjoyed it. Very exotic.
我查过留言 约书亚没打来
Well, I just checked our messages, and Joshua didn't call.
我还以为我没去他会担心
I mean, you would think he'd be worried about me not showing up.
更糟的是 罗斯正在佛蒙特风流快活
Ugh. And you know what makes it worse? Ross is all happy in Vermont.
拜托 你在看脱衣舞耶
Come on, look where you are.
- 再来轮   - 记得我要汽水
- Another round of daiquiris.     - Remember, virgin for me, please.
记得提醒我问那个人的名字
Oh, and don't let me leave without getting the name of that carpet guy.
拜托
Oh, come on.
算了 我要回家打给凯西
You know what? I'm just gonna go home and call Kathy.
如果有用的话 不 那是个考验
- Well, if you think it'll help.     - No. That was a test.
再过几小时我会喝醉想打给她
In a couple hours, I'm gonna get drunk and wanna call Kathy...
你们得阻止我
...and you have to stop me.
接着我会烂醉到想打给珍妮丝
Then I'm gonna be so drunk, I'm gonna wanna call Janice.
- 你是该打 她好吗？ - 噢
- You should. How is she?     - Oh!
有人需要再来一次性感热舞喔
I think somebody needs another lap dance.
谁在里面？
Hello? Who's in there?
你好吗？
How you doing?
你是谁？
Who in the hell are you?
我说寇克道格拉斯 你不会信吧？
Uh, guess you wouldn't believe me if I said I was Kirk Douglas, huh?
把裤子穿上 我好踹你的屁股
Put some pants on, kid, so I can kick your butt.
不 等等 你有所不知
No, no, no, wait. You don't understand.
我是个演员
See, I'm an actor.
乔伊崔比亚尼 今天跟你有一场戏
Joey Tribbiani. I'm doing a scene with you today.
但是我很臭(演得很烂)
And, well, I stink.
你有演这部片？ 对
- You're in this picture?     - Yeah, yeah.
我演不肯跟你合作的警察 因为你很我行我素
I'm one of the cops who won't work with you because you're a loose cannon.
总之我很抱歉 但我真的很臭(演得很烂)
Anyway, look, I'm really sorry, but I just... I stink.
- 乔伊 是吧？ - 对
- Joey, right?     - Yeah.
每个演员或多或少…
Every actor, one time or another... Ah.
都会觉得自己烂
Every actor thinks he stinks.
连劳伦斯奥立佛 有时也会这么想
Even Laurence Olivier sometimes thought he stank.
- 劳勃瑞福根本不看自己演戏   - 不 你没听懂
- Bob Redford won't even watch himself.     - No, no, no, you don't understand.
- 听我说   - 是
- Listen to me.     - No... Yeah.
每一个好演员…
I don't know one actor worth his salt...
在演艺生涯中都曾说过 "天哪 我真烂"
...who one time in his career didn't say, "God, I stink."
我刚拍完一场戏 第一镜 我演得烂透了
Hell, I just did a scene out there. First take, I stunk the place up.
重要的是你要记住
But the important thing that you must remember...
不管你认为自己有多烂
...no matter how badly you think you stink...
也不能闯进我的休息室 用我的浴室
...you must never, ever bust into my dressing room and use my shower.
懂了吗？
Do you understand me?
- 很抱歉   - 等 是等
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir. I'm very sorry.     - Wait a minute.
- 把裤子带走   - 是
- Take your pants.     - Yeah. Oh, yeah.
我们表现得还好吧？ 好得很
- So we did okay at the strip club, right?     - Oh, yeah. That was great.
你们让最性感的服务生
Thanks to you, the hottest waitress there is quitting...
要辞职去当小学老师
...to teach the third grade.
他居然还没打来
I can't believe it. He still hasn't called.
- 约许吗？ - 是约书亚
- Who, Josh?     - It's "Joshua."
- 他不喜欢约许？ - 是我不喜欢
- What, he doesn't like "Josh"?     - No, I don't.
我要把运动裤换回来
All right. Well, I'm gonna put my sweats back on.
不要啦 你说得对
No, wait. You know what? You were right.
我们当男生当得不好 你知道为什么吗？
We really weren't great at being guys. But do you know why?
因为我们是女生
Because we're girls.
- 所以呢？ - 你知道女生最擅长什么吗？
- Yeah.     - Do you know what girls are good at?
跳脱衣舞
Stripping.
不 是倾听 坐下
No, listening. Sit.
如果你肯一吐为快 或许就没事了
You know, maybe it would really, really help if you would just talk.
是啊 你的心在想什么？
Yeah, come on. What's going on in there?
你想哭也没关系
And you know, if you wanna cry, that's okay too.
我要请你们都离开
Okay, look, I'm gonna have to ask you all to leave.
别这样嘛 钱德
Come on, Chandler.
算了 我们试过了 但第三阶段没希望了
Look, forget it. We tried, but phase three is a lost cause.
那些舞娘都很辣
Those strippers were insanely hot...
我却无法产生性幻想
...and I couldn't picture myself with any of them.
她们真的很漂亮
They really were pretty, weren't they?
- 我喜欢一号战斗机驾驶   - 糖糖？
- I really liked that fighter pilot one.     - Oh, Candy?
- 她好有劲   - 对啊
- Oh, she was so spunky.     - Yeah.
要是我要跟女人在一起…
You know, I think if I were gonna be with a woman...
我会选蜜雪充那型的
...it'd be with someone like Michelle.
她好娇小
She was... Oh, she was just so petite.
我会选香姐
See, I don't know. For me, it would have to be Chantal.
没错 香姐
- Oh, Chantal, yeah.     - Chantal.
对啊 天哪…
You know? Oh, my God. The... Oh.
她的皮肤好嫩
She had the smoothest skin.
我塞钱给她时 手擦过她的大腿…
I mean, when I stuck that dollar bill in her G-string and grazed her thigh...
第三阶段
Phase three!
我进入第三阶段了
I just achieved phase three!
真的？
Really?
我可以想像你们跟她们在一起
I am totally picturing you with all those women.
- 那不是第三阶段    - 我也在场
- That's not phase three.     - Well, I'm there too.
- 我们在闲性派对吗？ - 别说了 我快疯了
- Well, are we all together in a group?     - Stop it, you're killing me.
我进入第四阶段了
I think I just moved on to phase four.
- 那是什么？ - 我再也不想谈恋爱
- Oh, what is that?     - Where I don't want a relationship ever.
只想跟脱衣舞娘和朋友上床
I just wanna have sex with strippers and my friends.
来嘛 让我看看你的笑容
Come on. Let me see that smile.
我不想笑
I don't wanna.
拜托啦？
Please?
人家想看脱衣舞嘛
I wanted to go to the strip club.
你有的是机会
You're gonna have plenty of chances, okay?
有成千上万的女人等着伤害我
There are thousands of women out there who are just waiting to screw me over.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
这周玩得怎样？
Hey. Ooh, how was Vermont?
艾蜜莉真是太棒了
Emily is incredible.
她好得无法形容
I mean, there are no words to describe her.
整个周末就像一场梦
The whole weekend was like a dream.
- 还有你 瑞秋 嘿   - 噢 嘿
- Oh. And you. Rach. Hey.     - Oh, hey.
你说得点也没错 什么？
- You were so right.     - What?
你说我们总算到了一个
What you said about us finally being in a place...
可以彼此祝福的阶段
...where we could really be happy for each other.
- 呃   - 我…
- Hmm.     - I mean, I...
- 我原本没那么放得开   - 哦
- I admit, I wasn't quite there.     - Mm-hm.
想到你和那个约许…
You know, I mean, the thought of you and that Josh guy...
- 约书亚   - 约书亚在俱乐部里…
- "Joshua."     - Joshua guy at that club...
跳舞狂欢
...dancing, having a good time.
我就觉得…
And the thought of it kind of...
- 你懂吗？ - 懂
- You know?     - Yeah.
但现在… 我完全放开了
But now, but now, I'm totally there.
我终于跟你一样了
I'm finally where you are.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank goodness.
谢谢你把艾蜜莉介绍给我
Yeah, and thank you for Emily.
不客气 我乐得帮忙
Oh, no problem. I'm so glad I could help, you know?
我很替你开心
I'm happy for you.
我才替你开心
Happy for you.
不 我才替你开心
Oh, no, happy for you.
好 接下来是这样
All right, ladies, here's what we're gonna do.
你帮我脱衣服
You are gonna take off my clothes.
你们两个去拿精油
You two go get the oils.
你就一直兴奋的叫
And you constantly scream at the top of your voice:
"吾王钱德万岁 "
"Chandler's the king! Chandler's the king!"
我想跟她在一起 我喜欢她
No, I wanna be with her. I like her.
没问题 大家随意
Oh, that's fine. Go with your instincts. Go with your instincts.
我要做什么？
Wait, what am I doing again?
专心一点 我随时都会醒来
Would you please pay attention? I could wake up at any moment.
嗨 我是约书亚 我来接瑞秋
Hi, I'm Joshua. I'm here to pick up Rachel.
他不是约书亚
No, no, no, that's not Joshua.
你想怎样？我又没见过他
What do you want from me? I never met the guy.
可惜你要走了 我们还有很多事要忙
So anyway, Rachel, I'm sorry you can't stay. The rest of us have a lot of work to do.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
好 我得醒过来
All right, listen, I gotta wake up.